Luis Horcajo

luishorcajomoreno@gmail.com +34636213629

Portfolio LinkedIn

ABOUT



I am a multidisciplinary designer with a unique perspective and strong problem solving skills. I aim to create a more socially engaged community by shaping digital experiences in both the cultural and commercial industries. I care about finding innovative solutions by deeply understanding the people around me and the worlds they live in.

EMPLOYMENT

MICHAEL KORS, GLASHÜTTE ORIGINAL & LOUIS VUITTON — SALES ADVISOR

November 2014 - January 2020

Offering personal advice to local and foreign customers, building customer loyalty and strategizing and rolled out initiatives to improve company standards and customer experience.

VIERNES COMUNICACIÓN — GRAPHIC DESIGNER

October 2013 - October 2014

Working as the main graphic designer within a small team of three creative directors in the communication field, social innovation and inclusivity. Improving my visual designing skills, working with deadlines and growing in a team.

ADVIRA BEYOND, KUO EXPERIENCE & TELLING INSIGHT — COOLHUNTER

January 2009 - October 2014

Providing advice and perspective as a consumer and trendsetter to marketing companies, collaborating with them to create new product research, trends and ways of consumption.

EDUCATION

IRONHACK — UX/UI DESIGN

April 2020

A 24 weeks bootcamp learning the fundamentals of User Centered Design.

SALESIANOS — GRAPHIC DESIGN

June 2015

4 years of learning the elementary principles of graphic design.

LANGUAGES

TOOLS

Figma, Sketch, Invision, Principle, Adobe Creative Suite, HTML/CSS.

SKILLS

DESIGN & CORE BUSINESS

Design & innovation processes, end-to-end & iterative design, research, benchmarking & brand positioning.

SOFT

Communication - Team player - Creativity Excitement - Equality - People - Empathy